Guide to the Minister to the University (Dean of the Chapel) records, 1940-1984 UA.17.02.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Minister to the University (Dean of the Chapel) records
1940-1984
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Duke University. Dean of the Chapel
UA.17.02.0001
30.5 Linear Feet
The dean of Duke Chapel oversees the operation of the chapel and plays an integral role in connecting the academic and spiritual lives of the university's students, faculty and staff. The collection contains materials of the Minister's office, the Chaplain, Duke University Church, Friends of Duke Chapel, student religious activities and organization. Materials include files on former preachers at Duke Chapel, photographs, pamphlets, clippings, correspondence and audio cassettes. Materials range in date from 1940-1984.
Access Restrictions
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
Collection is open for research.
For a period of twenty-five years from the origin of the material, permission in writing from the office of origin and the University Archivist is required for use. After twenty-five years, records that have been processed may be consulted with the permission of the University Archivist.
In off-site storage; 48 hours advance notice is required for use.
Provenance
The Minister to the University (Dean of the Chapel) records were received by the University Archives as transfers over a period of time.
Biographical/Historical note
The position of Minister of the University has undergone several title changes and reporting lines since it was first filled in 1932, the same year the Chapel was first used. While the Chapel was being constructed, President Few specified that it should be non-denominational and that services should not include the usual ceremony and hymn-singing of Protestant churches. Few later modified this approach, but the non-denominational focus was kept.
Initially two professors in the School of Religion, Franklin Hickman and Elbert Russell served as the first Preachers to the University. In late 1937, the campus approved the formation of an interdenominational congregation to be associated with Chapel and the Student Religious Council recommended the employment of a full-time university minister. As a result, Hickman was named the first Dean of the Chapel in 1938. Hickman shared preaching duties with James Cleland after the Divinity School hired him as professor of preaching in 1945. In 1948, Hickman recommended the "Dean of the Chapel" title be abolished, since it was a deanship in name only. Cleland protested but did not gain the deanship title until 1956, after Hickman retired.
When Cleland retired and Wilkerson left to become president of Greensboro College, Robert Young was appointed to the newly named Minister to the University position. A 1972 campus study of the dean and chaplain positions done in advance of Cleland's retirement recommended the change. William Willimon was hired as Minister to the University in 1984, and the Board of Trustees changed his title to Dean of the Chapel in 1989. Willimon, like Cleland, served as a professor in the Divinity School.
Preacher to the University
1932-38 Franklin S. Hickman, Methodist
1933-37 Elbert Russell, Quaker
1949-55 James T. Cleland, Presbyterian
Dean of the Chapel
1938-48 Franklin S. Hickman
1956-73 James T. Cleland
1983 Robert T. Young, honorary title given after resignation, Methodist
1989-2004 William H. Willimon, Methodist
2005-Present Samuel Wells, Anglican
Chaplain
1954-57 Barney L. Jones, Methodist
Chaplain to the University
1958-1972 Howard Wilkinson, Methodist
Minister to the University
1973-83 Robert T. Young
1984-89 William H. Willimon
Scope and Contents note
Historically, the role of the dean of Duke Chapel has changed as has the title. Currently, the dean of Duke Chapel oversees the operation of the chapel and plays an integral role in connecting the academic and spiritual lives of the university's students, faculty and staff. In addition to overseeing planned worship, counseling and preaching, the dean serves as a focal point for ethical and theological discussions on campus covering a wide range of topical issues. The collection contains materials of the Minister's office, the Chaplain, Duke University Church, Friends of Duke Chapel, student religious activities and organization. Materials include files on former preachers at Duke Chapel, photographs, pamphlets, clippings, correspondence and audio cassettes. Materials range in date from 1940-1984.
Boxes 1-10 contain A84-22. Box 11 contains A83-76 and A84-25. Boxes 12-13 contain A84-25. Box 14 contains A84-25 and A84-99. Boxes 15-18 contain A84-99. Boxes 19-20 contain A99-64. Box 21 contains A97-41.
Related Material
James T. Cleland Papers, Duke University Archives, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University.
Duke University Chapel Recordings [sound and video recordings], Duke University Archives, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University.
Fellowship of Christian Athletes, Duke University Chapter Records, Duke University Archives, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University.
Elbert Russell Papers, Duke University Archives, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University.
Friends of Duke Chapel Records, Duke University Archives, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University.
Methodism; Chaplains; Duke University -- History -- 20th century; Duke University -- Religion; Duke University -- Religious activities; Duke University -- Students; Duke University. Chapel -- Organs; Duke University. Chapel; YMCA of the USA
- Baptist Student Union, 1950-1954 (Box 1)
- Baptist Student Union, 1955-1957 (Box 1)
- Christian Science Organization, 1955-1957 (Box 1)
- Duke Christian Fellowship, 1955-1960 (Box 1)
- Denominational Groups Miscellaneous, 1957 (Box 1)
- Episcopal Student Fellowship, Canterbury Club, 1953-1957 (Box 1)
- Hillel Foundation, Jewish, 1952-1956 (Box 1)
- Kappa Chi, Pre-Ministerial Fraternity, 1955-1957 (Box 1)
- Lutheran Student Association, 1952-1957 (Box 1)
- Methodist Student Fellowship, 1955-1957 (Box 1)
- Methodist Student Fellowship, 1954-1955 (Box 1)
- Methodist Student Fellowship, 1953-1955 (Box 1)
- Methodist Student Fellowship, 1953-1957 (Box 1)
- Newman Club, Catholic, 1953-1957 (Box 1)
- Presbyterian Westminster Fellowship, 1953-1957 (Box 1)
- School of Nursing Vespers, 1952-1957 (Box 1)
- Duke-Durham Unitarian Fellowship, 1953-1957 (Box 1)
- Society of Friends, Quaker, 1955-1957 (Box 1)
- United Student Fellowship, 1956-1957 (Box 1)
- United Student Fellowship, 1952-1956 (Box 1)
- Methodist Student Movement, 1954-1956 (Box 1)
- Methodist Student Movement, 1951-1955 (Box 1)
- YMCA - Minutes, 1955-1956 (Box 1)
- YMCA - Dad's Day, 1955-1957 (Box 1)
- YMCA - Local Reports, 1953-1956 (Box 1)
- Y Retreat Center, 1955-1957 (Box 1)
- YMCA - YWCA, 1957 (Box 1)
- YMCA - YWCA, 1955-1957 (Box 1)
- Y Correspondence, 1956-1957 (Box 2)
- Y Correspondence, 1955-1956 (Box 2)
- YMCA Comm. Sings, undated (Box 2)
- York Bible Class, 1955-1957 (Box 2)
- Administration - Rules, Procedure and Forms, 1952-1956 (Box 2)
- Affiliate Member Dorm List, undated (Box 2)
- American Friends Service Committee, 1955-1956 (Box 2)
- Approved Supply Pastors' School, 1954 (Box 2)
- Calendar of School Year, 1954-1958 (Box 2)
- Campus Chest, 1953-1955 (Box 2)
- Choir, 1955-1956 (Box 2)
- Commencement, 1954-1957 (Box 2)
- Conferences, 1953-1957 (Box 2)
- Constitution of the Men's Association of Trinity College, undated (Box 2)
- Cornell - United Religious Work, 1956 (Box 2)
- Danforth Fellows, 1954-1956 (Box 2)
- Denominational Centers, 1951 (Box 2)
- Denominational Supper Clubs Retreat Policies, Etc., 1953-1955 (Box 2)
- Durham Ministerial Association, 1955 (Box 2)
- Easter Sunrise Service, 1952-1958
  - A. Lent: Lenten Vespers, Holy Week, Good Friday, Etc. (Box 2)
  - B. Easter Sunrise Service (Box 2)
  - C. Unmarked (Box 2)
  - D. Special Observances, Lenten Vespers - 1958 (Box 2)
  - E. Special Observances, Noonday Meditations - 1958 (Box 2)
  - F. Easter Sunrise Service (Box 2)
- Engagements: Visitors, 1954-1955 (Box 2)
- Fraternities, 1953-1956 (Box 2)
- Funerals, 1954-1955 (Box 2)
- Foreign Students, 1955 (Box 2)
- Founder's Day, 1954 (Box 2)
- God's Holy Temple, 1956 (Box 2)
- Hymnals, 1954-1955 (Box 2)
- Inter-Collegiate Fellowship, 1956-1957 (Box 2)
- Inter-faith Dinner, 1953-1954 (Box 2)
- Interfraternity Service of Dedication, 1956-1957 (Box 2)
- Japan International Christian University, 1951-1957 (Box 2)
- The Lisle Fellowship, 1954-1957 (Box 2)
- Men's Student Government Assn., 1952-1954 (Box 2)
- Methodist Board of Education, 1952-1956 (Box 2)
- Methodist Youth Fellowship, 1955-1957 (Box 2)
- Miscellaneous, 1952-1958 (Box 2)
- Miscellaneous Reports, 1955-1957 (Box 2)
- Missions and Mission Projects, 1955 (Box 2)
- Motive, 1955-1956 (Box 2)
- Project Nicaragua, 1966, 1964-1966 (Box 2)
- National Association of Colleges and University Chaplains, 1952-1957 (Box 2)
- National Council of Churches of Christ in America, 1954-1957 (Box 2)
- National Council on Religion in Higher Education, 1954-1957 (Box 2)
- North Carolina Council of Churches, 1953-1956 (Box 2)
- Organ Recital, 1957 (Box 2)
- Orientation Week, 1951-1956 (Box 2)
- Committee on Personal and Family Living, 1956 (Box 2)
- Phi Beta Kappa, 1953-1954 (Box 2)
- Photos, circa 1954 (Box 2)
- Photos: Religious Life Handbook, 1954 (Box 2)
- Photographs: Religious Life Handbook, 1954-1955 (Box 2)
- Photographs: Religious Life Staff and Ministry of Worship, circa 1950s (Box 2)
- Preministerial Scholarship Committee, 1955-1956 (Box 2)
- Race [Contents: Charles C. Spaulding], 1943-1948 (Box 2)
- Requests for Information (Box 3)
- Recommendations, 1956-1957 (Box 3)
- Religious Life Personnel - Acting Associate Director, 1956-1957 (Box 3)
- Chaplain to Methodist Students, 1955 (Box 3)
- Choir Director, 1955-1956 (Box 3)
- Dean of the Chapel, 1955-1957 (Box 3)
- Dean Cannon, 1955 (Box 3)
- The President [Contents: A. Hollis Edens], 1955-1958 (Box 3)
- Religious Activities Staff, 1953-1957 (Box 3)
- Religious Life Staff Procurement, 1955-1957 (Box 3)
- Associate Director of Religious Life: West, 1955-1956 (Box 3)
- Vice President [Contents: H.J. Herring], 1956-1957 (Box 3)
- Acting Chaplain, 1956-1957 (Box 3)
- Chaplain to the University, 1955-1957 (Box 3)
- University Carilloneur, 1955-1956 (Box 3)
- Associate Director of Religious Life: East, 1955-1957 (Box 3)
- University Organist, 1955-1956 (Box 3)
- Special Observance Committee (Box 3)
- Lenten Vespers - Actual Programs, 1958 (Box 3)
- Sex Knowledge Inventory, 1953 (Box 3)
- Scholarships and Fellowships, 1956 (Box 3)
- Sermons, undated (Box 3)
- Group Study, Davidson Conference, 1957 (Box 3)
- Student Volunteer Movement, 1952-1956 (Box 3)
- Summer Projects, 1951-1954 (Box 3)
- United Student Christian Council, 1954-1957 (Box 3)
- University Christian Mission, 1952-1956 (Box 3)
- Appropriate Music for Weddings, 1959 (Box 3)
- Weddings, 1955-1960 (Box 3)
- World Council of Churches, 1954-1957 (Box 3)
- World Student Christian Federation United Student Christian Council, 1954-1957 (Box 3)
- World Student Christian Federation United Student Christian Council, 1947-1955 (Box 3)
- World University Service, 1952-1957 (Box 3)
- Junior Ministers' Instructions Senior Ministers' Instructions, 1956-1957 (Box 3)
- Committee Correspondence: Communion, 1955-1956 (Box 3)
- Suggested Guest Preachers, 1949-1957 (Box 3)
- Preaching Schedule, 1957-1958 (Box 3)
- Preaching Schedule, 1956-1957 (Box 3)
- Howard - Misc., 1956-1959 (Box 4)
- Committee Correspondence: Pulpit, 1951-1957 (Box 4)
- Preaching Schedule - Summer, 1957 (Box 4)
- YMCA, 1958-1959 (Box 4)
- Music - Handwritten, undated (Box 4)
- Ecumenical Press Service, 1955-1957 (Box 4)
- Church Board Minutes, 1955-1956 (Box 4)
- Campus Organization Officers, 1955 (Box 4)
- Religious Life Handbook, 1954-1955 (Box 4)
- Jewish Student Group - The Hillel Society, 1957 (Box 4)
- Sexism Survives, 1971-1973 (Box 4)
- Gay Material and Films, 1971 (Box 4)
- National Y Correspondence, 1973 (Box 4)
- General Y Info., 1972-1974 (Box 4)
- Racism - Supportive Climate, 1970's (Box 4)
- Racism at Duke, 1970's (Box 4)
- White Action Study Project, 1971-1972 (Box 4)
- Financial Aid, 1975-1976 (Box 4)
- Admissions, 1973-1974 (Box 4)
- Race - Misc., 1969-1971 (Box 4)
- Angela Davis, 1971-1972 (Box 4)
- Legal Defense/Const. Rights Funds, 1974-1975 (Box 4)
- Militanism/W.R.L./CCCO, 1974-1976 (Box 4)
- Women/Sexism, 1975 (Box 4)
- Criminal Justice, 1975 (Box 4)
- Capital Punishment/Petition Materials, undated (Box 4)
- Capital Punishment/Death Penalty, 1975 (Box 4)
- Butner, circa 1975 (Box 4)
- North Carolina Prisoners' Union and Other N. C. Resource People, circa 1975 (Box 4)
- Advisory Board - Minutes, 1971-1972 (Box 4)
- Afro-Americans, 1971-1972 (Box 4)
- Advisory Board, 1971-1972 (Box 4)
- Annual Report, 1971-1972 (Box 4)
- Association Demands, 1971-1972 (Box 4)
- Bazaar, 1971-1972 (Box 4)
- Cabinets Meetings, 1971-1972 (Box 4)
- Campus Ministry, 1971-1972 (Box 4)
- Committee for a Broaden Perspective at Duke, 1971-1972 (Box 4)
- County Hospital Issue, 1972 (Box 4)
- Dean Griffith Staff Large and Small, 1971-1972 (Box 4)
- Dean Staff - Women's College, 1971-1972 (Box 4)
- Draft Counseling, 1971-1972 (Box 4)
- Drugs and Dope, 1971-1972 (Box 4)
- Duke University Christian Council, 1971-1972 (Box 4)
- Y Elections, 1971-1972 (Box 4)
- Executive Meetings, 1971-1972 (Box 4)
- Flyers, 1971-1972 (Box 4)
- Freshman Week, 1971-1972 (Box 4)
- General Information, 1971-1972 (Box 4)
- Great American Peace Machine, 1971-1972 (Box 4)
- Committee on Human Sexuality, 1971-1972 (Box 5)
- Indian Conference - October, 1971 (Box 5)
- Institutional Maintenance, 1971-1972 (Box 5)
- Miscellaneous, 1971-1972 (Box 5)
- National YWCA, 1971-1972 (Box 5)
- Newsletters, 1971-1972 (Box 5)
- Notices of Meetings, 1971-1972 (Box 5)
- Retreats, 1971-1972 (Box 5)
- Student Immigration Collective, 1971-1972 (Box 5)
- Tutoring Experiment, 1971-1972 (Box 5)
- University Experience - Summer 1971 (Box 5)
- YM-YWCA Constitution, 1973-1974 (Box 5)
- Lettuce Boycott, 1972 (Box 5)
- Racism Conference at Duke, 1972 (Box 5)
- Sexism Workshop, 1972 (Box 5)
- Sexism - Women's Group, 1972-1973 (Box 5)
- INSA, 1971-1974 (Box 5)
- Day Care, 1969-1974 (Box 5)
- Housing Campaign, 1967-1969 (Box 5)
- Portrait of a Southern City - History, 1967 (Box 5)
- Boycott of Durham Merchants, 1968 (Box 5)
- Institute for Nonviolent Study and Action, 1972-1973 (Box 5)
- The University Experience, 1972-1973 (Box 5)
- Farmworkers, 1970's (Box 5)
- Gay Workshop - Staff, 1971-1973 (Box 5)
- Anti-Abortion, 1978 (Box 5)
- Pro-Abortion, 1976-1978 (Box 5)
- Amnesty International, 1977 (Box 5)
- Campaign to Stop Government Spying, 1977-1978 (Box 5)
- Durham - Meals on Wheels, 1977 (Box 5)
- Environment - Energy, 1976-1978 (Box 5)
- FFP, 1977-1978 (Box 5)
- Handguns, 1978 (Box 5)
- Hunger Resources - Information, Articles, Orgs., 1977-1978 (Box 5)
- Hunger - Bibliographies, etc., 1976-1978 (Box 5)
- Inst. World Order, 1978 (Box 5)
- LUCHA - Christians Concerned for Chile, 1978 (Box 5)
- Non-Violence/Center for Conflict Resolution, 1977-1978 (Box 5)
- Nuclear, 1976-1978 (Box 5)
- Resources, 1977-1978 (Box 5)
- Social Action Groups, 1977 (Box 5)
- Past Social Issues - Panama Canal, 1978 (Box 5)
- Pending Social Issues, 1978 (Box 5)
- Socialism, 1975 (Box 5)
- Third World, undated (Box 5)
- Unions, 1974-1978 (Box 5)
- Racism, 1969-1978 (Box 5)
- Rural Issues, 1973-1978 (Box 5)
- 22 Audio Cassette Tapes (Box 5)
- Religion Questionnaire, 1964 (Box 6)
- Harold A Williams, 1972 (Box 6)
- Linoscribe, 1960-1963 (Box 6)
- Fund Raising, 1971 (Box 6)
- Office Machines, 1971 (Box 6)
- Founders' Day, 1972 (Box 6)
- Use of University Facilities, 1971 (Box 6)
- Personnel, 1968-1970 (Box 6)
- Executive Committee, 1972 (Box 6)
- Chapel, East Arch, 1971 (Box 6)
- Draft, 1972 (Box 6)
- Communion - Procedure and Information, 1959 (Box 6)
- Communion, 1958-1969 (Box 6)
- World Council of Churches Office, 1968-1970 (Box 6)
- Preaching Schedule, Duke Chapel, 1957-1970 (Box 6)
- Summer Pulpit, 1970-1971 (Box 6)
- Pulpit Comm., 1956-1966 (Box 6)
- Summer Pulpit, 1957-1967 (Box 6)
- Fall-Spring Preachers, 1958-1972 (Box 6)
- Myron S. Augsburger, 1971 (Box 6)
- Browne Barr, 1969 (Box 6)
- Bishop Stephen F. Bayne, Jr., 1971 (Box 6)
- Eugene Carson Blake, 1957 (Box 6)
- Jerald C. Brauer, 1961 (Box 6)
- J. Russell Chandran, 1972 (Box 6)
- Wm. S. Coffin, 1967 (Box 6)
- Charles A Coulson, 1963 (Box 6)
- Evans E. Crawford, 1967 (Box 6)
- G. Henton Davies, 1969 (Box 6)
- L. Harold DeWolf, 1966 (Box 6)
- Nels F. S. Ferre, 1960 (Box 6)
- Valdo Galland, 1978 (Box 6)
- Dean Samuel Gandy, 1965 (Box 6)
- John Garrett, 1967 (Box 6)
- Bishop Earl G. Hunt, Jr., 1966 (Box 6)
- John A. Hutchinson, 1959 (Box 6)
- Philip A. Johnson, 1968 (Box 6)
- Dow Kirkpatrick, 1969 (Box 6)
- Jorge Lara-Braud, 1971 (Box 6)
- Jason M. Lawson, Jr., 1971 (Box 6)
- Robert E. Luccock, 1962-1970 (Box 6)
- John D. Maguire, 1966 (Box 6)
- Bishop Rafah Manikam, 1966 (Box 6)
- Principal John Marsh, 1958 (Box 6)
- Jose Miguez-Bonino, 1968 (Box 6)
- A.T. Mollegen, 1961 (Box 6)
- Jurgen D. Moltmann, 1967 (Box 6)
- Colin Morris, 1972 (Box 6)
- Walter G. Muelder, 1963 (Box 6)
- Martin Niemoller, 1968 (Box 6)
- Harold Ockenga, 1970 (Box 6)
- Edward H. Patey, 1971 (Box 6)
- C.A. Pennington, 1971 (Box 6)
- J.F. Peter, 1959 (Box 6)
- Harry M. Philpott, 1970 (Box 6)
- Joachim Poillai O.M.I., 1972 (Box 6)
- Liston Pope, 1962 (Box 6)
- Bishop W. Kenneth Pope, 1963 (Box 6)
- Bishop Richard C. Raines, 1960 (Box 6)
- E.C. Reckard, 1966-1970 (Box 6)
- Elfan Rees, 1963 (Box 6)
- Milton Robinson, 1967 (Box 6)
- Ruth Rohlfs, 1971 (Box 6)
- Culbert Rutenber, 1969 (Box 6)
- Eduard Schweizer, 1970 (Box 6)
- Roger L. Shinn, post 1954 (Box 6)
- Joseph Sittler, 1962 (Box 6)
- Eugene Smith, 1964 (Box 6)
- Douglas Steere, 1962 (Box 6)
- Edmund Steimle, 1971-1972 (Box 6)
- Bishop W. McF. Stowe, 1969 (Box 6)
- Elton Trueblood, 1968 (Box 6)
- Bishop Raimundo Valenzuela, 1972 (Box 6)
- T. Paul Verghese, 1968 (Box 6)
- Alan Walker, 1968 (Box 6)
- J.S. Whale, 1960-1968 (Box 6)
- Sam S. Wiley, 1969-1970 (Box 6)
- Colin Williams, 1955-1969 (Box 6)
- Summer School Preachers (Box 6)
- Peter E.A. Addo, 1970 (Box 6)
- Purnell Bailey, 1959 (Box 6)
- Anwar Barkat, 1972 (Box 6)
- John Carlton, 1968-1972 (Box 6)
- Warren Carr, 1965 (Box 6)
- Paul Carruth, 1963 (Box 6)
- Rob. A. Davis, 1968-1969 (Box 6)
- Mark Depp, 1961 (Box 6)
- Bishop Thomas A. Fraser, Jr., 1963 (Box 6)
- Wallace Fridy, 1965 (Box 6)
- Bishop W. Kenneth Goodson, 1957 (Box 6)
- H. Grady Hardin, 1966 (Box 6)
- H. Gordon Harland, 1969 (Box 6)
- C.C. Herbert, Jr., 1963 (Box 6)
- Jason G. Higgin, 1960 (Box 6)
- Peter Klopfer, 1965-1967 (Box 6)
- John E. Lawrence, 1970 (Box 6)
- Don M. Mackay, 1967 (Box 6)
- G. Robert McKenzie, Jr., 1970 (Box 6)
- Russ T. Montfort, 1970 (Box 6)
- E.H. Nease, 1972 (Box 6)
- Norman Olds, 1969 (Box 6)
- Eugene Peacock, 1967 (Box 6)
- Richard L. Sommers, 1972 (Box 6)
- J. Lem Stokes, 1959-1970 (Box 6)
- David Swain, 1965 (Box 6)
- Chas. T. Thrift, Jr., 1963 (Box 6)
- R.G. Tuttle, Jr., 1964 (Box 6)
- T. Marvin Vick, Jr., 1964 (Box 6)
- Chapel Guest Preachers, 1973 (Box 6)
- Hugh Anderson, 1968-1973 (Box 6)
- Allan T. Burry, 1973 (Box 6)
- Charles Henderson, 1973 (Box 6)
- Robert Johnson, 1973 (Box 6)
- Thomas A. Langford, 1973 (Box 6)
- Sr. Elizabeth McAlister, 1971-1973 (Box 6)
- Dr. Samuel Proctor, 1973 (Box 6)
- Isabel Rogers, 1973 (Box 6)
- Jack Shelton, 1973 (Box 6)
- A. John Wilson, III, 1973 (Box 6)
- Robert T. Young, 1973 (Box 6)
- Chaplains Files (Box 6)
- Carillon, 1958-1972 (Box 6)
- Candelabra, 1971 (Box 6)
- Recess Services, 1965 (Box 6)
- Fire in the Chapel, 22 January 1971 (Box 6)
- Choir Letters, from Ben Smith, 1969 (Box 6)
- Ben Smith, 1969-1972 (Box 6)
- David Hurd, 1972-1973 (Box 6)
- Organist, 1965-1969 (Box 6)
- Perspective Organists, 1967-1969 (Box 6)
- Chapel Student Volunteers, undated (Box 6)
- Chapel Concert Series, 1970-1972 (Box 6)
- Possible Church, 1971 (Box 6)
- Possible Duke U. Church, 1971 (Box 6)
- Daily Chapel, 1971 (Box 6)
- Nov. 12, 1972 Dance Service, 1972 (Box 6)
- Carolina Choir, 1971 (Box 6)
- Burlington Rotary Boys Choir, 1971-1972 (Box 6)
- Discovery and Praises, 1971 (Box 6)
- L'Enfant Prodigue, 16 January, 1972 (Box 6)
- Iain Hamilton An Epitaph..., 1972 (Box 6)
- Princeton University Chapel, 1965 (Box 6)
- Administrative Chapel Committee, 1951-1957 (Box 6)
- 1971 Lenten Organ Recitals, 1971-1972 (Box 6)
- Christ Lag in Todesbanden, 1970 (Box 6)
- Christmas Eve Service, 1970-1971 (Box 6)
- Christmas in Word and Music, 1963-1968 (Box 6)
- Amahl and the Night Visitors, 1965-1969 (Box 6)
- Attendant, 1968 (Box 6)
- Hostess, 1966-1971 (Box 6)
- Vestry, 1972 (Box 6)
- Chapel Brochure, 1966-1967 (Box 6)
- Group Flowers: Commencement, Weddings, 1968 (Box 6)
- Youth Day, 1971 (Box 6)
- Peace Service, 1968 (Box 6)
- Brass Players in Chapel, Easter, 1966 (Box 6)
- Chapel Machines, 1971 (Box 6)
- Air Conditioning Chapel, 1969 (Box 6)
- Crypt Safe Combination, 1967 (Box 6)
- Chapel Certificates, undated (Box 6)
- Wedding Application Forms, 1971 (Box 6)
- Weddings at Duke, undated (Box 6)
- Nursery, 1968 (Box 6)
- Chapel Attendance Hindrances, 1968 (Box 6)
- Sunday Luncheons Question Periods, 1965 (Box 6)
- Memorial Chapel Organ, 1957-1971 (Box 6)
- Communion Order Revision, 1965 (Box 6)
- C.B. Fisk, 1971 (Box 6)
- Kyanize Letter, 1972 (Box 6)
- Telephones in Chapel, 1968 (Box 6)
- Publicity, Chapel, 1971-1972 (Box 6)
- Publicity, Chapel II, 1972 (Box 7)
- Publicity, Chapel III, 1971 (Box 7)
- Chapel: 0pen at Night, 1960-1971 (Box 7)
- Keys, 1970 (Box 7)
- Reg. Schedule of Xian. Miss., 1972 (Box 7)
- Bone Jesu, 1971 (Box 7)
- Miscellaneous, 1971 (Box 7)
- M.B.D. Fdn. Grant 720-0414, 1969-1971 (Box 7)
- M.B.D. Fdn. Grant, IBM, 1968-1970 (Box 7)
- Misc. - Chapel, 1968-1971 (Box 7)
- Adm. Comm. of the Chapel, 1968-1969 (Box 7)
- Chaplain Wilkinson, 1970 (Box 7)
- Flentrop Organ, 1969-1971 (Box 7)
- Adm. Comm. of the Chapel, 1969-1970 (Box 7)
- Chapel Choir - Spring Oratorio 1970 - Estimated Expenses (Box 7)
- Adm. Comm. of the Chapel, 1966-1968 (Box 7)
- Chapel Lighting and Acoustics, 1957 (Box 7)
- Chapel Misc., 1962-1967 (Box 7)
- Visiting Artists, Singers, 1965 (Box 7)
- Acoustical Study, 1965-1969 (Box 7)
- Total Organ Comm, 1969 (Box 7)
- Memorial Chapel Maintenance Fund, 1973 (Box 7)
- Aeolian-Skinner, 1965-1971 (Box 7)
- Chapel Acoustics, 1966-1967 (Box 7)
- Aeolian-Skinner Organ, 1965-1967 (Box 7)
- Handel's Messiah Newspaper Ads, 1970 (Box 7)
- Messiah with Orchestra, 1965-1971 (Box 7)
- Administrative Comm. of the Chapel, 1964-1965 (Box 7)
- Salt Lake City Trip, 1962-1964 (Box 7)
- Music Dept. Proposal - Adm. Comm. of Chapel, 1962-1963 (Box 7)
- Chapel -- Christmas, 1945-1961 (Box 7)
- Administrative Committee of the Chapel, 1957-1970 (Box 7)
- Misc. Chaplain, 1965 (Box 7)
- Duke University Religious Council, 1963-1967 (Box 7)
- Budget, 1967-1968 (Box 7)
- DURC Budgets, 1962-1965 (Box 7)
- DURC Budget 73-0407-800, 1958-1966 (Box 7)
- Miscellaneous, 1966-1967 (Box 7)
- A.F.S.C., 1963-1964 (Box 7)
- Fiscal Policy Comm., 1958-1959 (Box 7)
- Union Theological Seminary, Manila, Phil., 1958-1963 (Box 7)
- Position Bond - D.U.R.C. Treas., 1967 (Box 7)
- Coordination and Planning Committee, 1957-1966 (Box 7)
- Interfaith and Fellowship, 1957-1963 (Box 7)
- Intercollegiate Fellowship, 1958-1961 (Box 7)
- Religious Life Handbook, 1957-1960 (Box 7)
- Pictures - Undated (Box 7)
- 1965 Handbook (Box 7)
- Published Annual Report (Box 7)
- 1958-1959 Report Volume: Ready for Publication (Box 7)
- DURC - Annual Reports, 1959-1960 (Box 7)